I am walking through the headquarters of
Prudential Vietnam Life Insurance Company
.  And now I'm going to tell
you a little story.  That was
my first day working at Prudential.
I stood in the elevator lobby, looking into the
mirror that read "Who is Bru," and
burst out laughing when I realized that
I was Bru.  From that moment on,
I believed I would be able to work
in an environment that valued
creativity.  I was right, because it was
here that I was able to nurture
my ideas and let them take flight.  I had the privilege of
steering that ship of ideas
through the challenges.  I was allowed to lead, I
was allowed to change, I was allowed to make mistakes, and I
was allowed to correct the
[music]
wrong.  Every door will open, every
barrier will be broken down, every distance
will be erased, and every doubt will
be illuminated by
integrity.  That lighthouse
guides every action of mine and yours,
enabling me to speak and act with
sincerity and a strong sense of responsibility.
At that time, I not only got to work
independently but also received absolute support
from everyone.  The spirit of collaboration
extends beyond the
same department, permeating every
corner of Prodential.
[Music]
Any problem I have is also
everyone's problem, so let's
share, solve, and learn together.
[Music]
Ask.  Trust me, opportunities arise from
adversity, success comes from
taking risks, and excellence comes to
those who never give up.  Because
this is where you will be listened to,
understood, and cared for.
This is where you can see that
your contributions truly
matter.  You are entitled to inherit
all the legacy that we are
wholeheartedly building day by day.  One of
those achievements is the
Best Workplace in Vietnam in the insurance industry award,
which we have worked extremely hard to
achieve for three consecutive years
[music]
.  Many of you are probably wondering
who I am to be able to say
these things.  When I joined Prudential, I
was simply one of the best candidates
selected.  And the working environment
at Prudential has helped me become the
best version of myself compared to
when I first started.  I was able to
always listen.  I have always been able to
understand.  I am inspired, and
I go on to inspire.  I am one of
over 1700 Prudential employees across all 63
provinces and cities who are exploring and improving
themselves.  I am Hung, I am Van, I am
Viet, I am Thanh, I am Mai, I am
Tuan, I am Binh, I am Phong.
We are Bru, and you can also
become a member of Pro Danential.
[music]